## Oliver Lee

(404) 492-5275 challengedev210@gmail.com

https://www.linkedin.com/in/oliver-lee-a40127254/

Talented and experienced front-end developer with 8+ years of experience executing with diverse skills. Enjoy working closely with team members with passion for both personal growth and for software development. Ready to apply my passion for coding to a talented engineering team to develop quality solutions.

## Professional experience

### Jr. React developer

02/2017 - 02/2018

#### **COMPUTAN, CANADA**

- Cooperate with designers to create clean interfaces and simple, intuitive interactions and experiences.
- Worked with design, product, and back-end teams to create 10 web products.
- Created 2 efficient and reusable front-end systems to drive web applications to marketplace.
- Used React to allow users to instantly update the medication list interface without reloading
- Utilized HTML, CSS, and Javascript to create 50+ responsive landing pages for both company and client.
- Work with senior developer to manage large, complex design projects for corporate clients.
- Complete detailed programming and development tasks for front end public and internal websites as well as challenging back-end server code.

## Vue.js developer for a VR Hardware Company

02/2018 - 05/2019

#### PICO INTERACTIVE, REMOTE

- Built several Vue.js web applications for VR products.
- Used different UI frameworks like Ant Design, Vuetify or Tailwind CSS based on the project design type.
- Integrated headless CSM and Butter CMS for pulling data and assets.

### Web developer

05/2019 - 01/2021

#### **BRUCE CLAY, JAPAN**

- Developed internal and external validation code using Javascript
- Designed mockup webpages and graphics in photo shop
- Built Rich Prototypes and Applications using HTML5,CSS3,Javascript,JQuery,Ajax,JSON,Angular.js and Bootstrap with MYSQL database
- Developed e-commerce website using Wordpress, Shopify
- Designed and developed web applications using CSS pre-processors such as Sass, Less.
- Involved in enhancing the application for client's requirement based on the market demand and updating in SharePoint using the MVC pattern, Angular.js, JQuery, Bootstrap, and Restful APIs.

### Full stack developer

01/2021 - 08/2022

### HIFI GAMING SOCIETY, US

- Collaborated and Developed HiFi DeFi gaming platform's all pages from dashboard to detailed every pages with several web developers.
- Converted NFT's figma design into separable UIs to compose different species of NFTs.

Designed and implemented the whole workflow and structure of gaming platform,
distributed tasks to members clearly as a lead developer.

## **Education**

#### UNIVERSITY OF TORONTO

2013-2017

Bachelor's Degree of computer science

## Skill Highlights

- 6 years of experience in progressive software development.
- Strong understanding of front-end frameworks(React, Angular, Vue, Next, Nuxt) and modern Javascript and Typescript concepts
- Advanced knowledge of API integration, orchestration and async design patterns.
- Experience with Material-UI, Figma, Typescript, Jira, Slack, Github, working with offshore team members
- Agile/scrum environment
- Excellent analytical, decision-making and problem-solving skill
- Ability to communicate well both verbally and in writing to technical and non-technical audiences of various levels within Black Knight or outside the organization

# Languages & Frameworks

## Languages

HTML, CSS, Javascript, Typescript, Php, Python, C, C#, Ruby

#### Frameworks

React.js, RoR, Vue.js, Angular.js, Next.js, Nuxt.js Svelte, Node.js, Express.js, Laravel, MongoDB, Django, MySQL